handsome eh dala you've gotten more handsome over the
guapo eh dala te has puesto más guapo
years eh you're like divine you eh
los años eh eres como divino tú eh
healthy relationship is more boring you
relación sana es más aburrida a ti te
like the Cook thing the cuc cuc cuc cuc cuc
gusta el rollo Cook el rollo cuc cuc cuc
cuc thing I have a wife maybe after
cuc tengo una esposa quizás después de
40 years maybe Well maybe I'll
40 años así capaz que Pues a lo mejor le
hire her a black guy There's Candela you
contrato un negro Ahí le de Candela tú
keep driving the Kia but in your mind
sigues yendo en el Kia pero en tu mente
you're in the Lamborghini you didn't even
tú estás en el Lamborghini ni siquiera
respond through your lawyer who
respondiste a través de tu abogado que
goes I escaped from trial no well every
va Yo escapé del juicio no bueno toda
Devil needs her criminal this is Hol
Diabla necesita su maliante esto es Hol
catches it on the fly or doesn't catch it that if I'm
coge al vuelo o no la coge que si soy
like the pg chat I have responses already
como el chat pg tengo respuestas ya
programmed you fit like a horse what a
programada calzas como caballo qué
bastard you are a horse for not you bastard
cabrón eres un caballo por no te cabrón
you have to delight people you know
tienes que deleitar a la gente tú sabes
I'm the godfather bastard if you get to Have
yo soy el padrino cabrón si llegas a Ten
a child someday it's like Georgina
un hijo algún día es como la Georgina
who said It's not that I don't like all children except
que dijo No es que a mí todos los niños
mine I have a
me caen mal menos los míos tengo una
cross tattooed but not upside down because I
cruz tatuada pero del revés no porque yo
look at it normal
me la miro normal
[Music]
[Música]